# Dai Katsu



linkedin.com/in/dai-katsu-star

## **Summary**

As an expert in Full Stack Development, From 2015 I have worked in the famous software companies as Blockchain Developer, Full Stack Software Engineer, Ecommerce Engineer, Project manager.

Provide my customers with the perfect front end and back end in which strong fashion and business style, gorgeousness and delicacy are in harmony.

### **Experience**



#### Ecommerce Developer & Project Manager

#### eagoats

May 2022 - Aug 2022 (4 months)

- I have got rich experience in building online stores by analyzing and monitoring customer experience and performing search engine optimization.
- Also, I could maximize my client's income by tracking store sales and customer visits.



#### **Full Stack Developer**

#### **CANNAVIGIA**

Sep 2021 - Apr 2022 (8 months)

- Ability to lead cross-functional team to realize the vision, taking into account business and technical requirements, constraints such as time, cost, and architecture tradeoffs.
- Highly organized, and efficient in a fast-paced, ever changing environments, able to prioritize effectively to accomplish objectives.

#### Blockchain Developer & Project Manager

#### NIPPON EXPRESS GROUP

Jul 2017 - Jun 2021 (4 years)

- I have rich experiences of building smart contracts for a lot of projects on various blockchain networks such as Ethereum, Binance Smart Cchain, polygon, Alorand, Solona, etc.
- Especially so far I have mostly kept on NFT crypto space like several kinds of games and NFT marketplace platforms using openzepplin ERC token standards like ERC-20, ERC-721, ERC-1155 tokens you know.

#### Full Stack Engineer

4K-Soft Ltd.

Sep 2015 - Jun 2017 (1 year 10 months)

- Worked with colleagues to set principles and patterns on the front-end and backend, design, develop, troubleshoot, debug, test, and ensure browser compatibility.

- Implemented professional code using PHP Framework, JavaScript Framework, CSS Framework, and Database Platform.
- Also consulted regularly with clients on project status, proposals, and technical issues

### **Education**



# The University of Tokyo

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Jul 2012 - Jun 2015

#### **Skills**

Team Leadership • Project Management • Interpersonal Communication • Blockchain • E-Commerce

- Web Development Mobile Application Development Game Development Responsive Web Design
- · Software Documentation